gomedia.us 2019-05-30

# Privacy - Go Media - Creativity at Work

Protecting your private information is a steadfast & ongoing priority at Go Media Inc. This Statement of Privacy applies to the gomedia.com and Go Media Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Go Media Inc. include gomedia.com, My Go Media and my.gomedia.us and The Go Media Arsenal, arsenal.gomedia.us. Go Media websites provide hosted solutions, professional services & digital resources. By using a Go Media website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### Collection of your Personal Information

Go Media may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Go Media's products and services, we collect billing, credit card information & potentially checking account information. This information is used to complete purchase transactions agreed to deliberately by you, the customer, explicitly through the action of standard E-commerce checkout or a contractual agreement set forth in writing by you and Go Media Inc.. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information related to your needs and transparently provided by you, the customer.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Go Media servers. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of a Go Media website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Go Media's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Go Media encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Go Media so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Go Media is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Go Media website.

#### Use of your Personal Information

Go Media collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Go Media may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Go Media. Go Media may contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

 **Go Media does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.**

Go Media may share general data with trusted vendors to help perform analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Go Media, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Go Media may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Go Media, in order to determine what Go Media services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Go Media to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Go Media will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Go Media or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Go Media; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Go Media, or the public.

#### Use of Cookies

The Go Media website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time, such as automatic completion of form fields or templates or to save user decisions for future use. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Go Media pages, or register with Go Media site or services, a cookie helps Go Media to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Go Media website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Go Media features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Go Media services or websites you visit.

#### Use of Cookies for Retargeting Measures

Go Media uses cookies from Google Analytics and Google AdWords to help us both advertise our services on the Internet. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on your activity on our website. This happens through the use of tracking cookies. These cookies do not collect identifiable information, nor gain access to your computer. You may opt-out of Google's use of cookies by updating your [ad settings](https://www.google.com/settings/). Thank you!

#### Security of your Personal Information

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Go Media uses the following:

  * Payment information is securely stored offsite by the PCI DSS compliant infrastructure provided by [Authorize.net Customer Information Manager](http://www.authorize.net/solutions/merchantsolutions/merchantservices/cim/).
  * Go Media E-commerce servers are maintained for PCI compliance with vulnerability testing performed quarterly by [Trustwave Holdings Inc](https://www.trustwave.com/).
  * [Geotrust](https://www.geotrust.com/), a Verisign company provides Go Media's 256 Bit SSL encryption certificate services. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. GeoTrust/Verisign is an independent, third-party company engaged in the development of digital trust. Verisign provides authentication of Internet services, digital identity and intellectual property.

#### Children Under Thirteen

Go Media does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Go Media by emailing support@gomedia.com. Please provide your full name, email address and physical address if applicable.

#### Changes to this Statement

Go Media will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Go Media encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Go Media is protecting your information.

#### Contact Information

Go Media welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Go Media has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Go Media at:

Go Media Inc.  
4507 Lorain Ave.  
Cleveland, Ohio 44102

Email Address:  
support@gomedia.com

Telephone number:  
+1-216-939-0000

Effective as of January 01, 2014
